http://www.largeprintreviews.com/privacy.html

Affiliate Disclosure: This site contains affiliate links, if you click on one of these links and make a purchase, we may receive a commission. Click here to learn more...
Large Print Reviews
Privacy Statement
Home | What's New | Reviews | Articles | Travel | Links | Search Large Print Bookstore | Low Vision Product Store
Large Print Reviews has created this privacy statement in order to
demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses our
information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Large Print Reviews.
This site contains links to other sites.
Large Print Reviews is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites.
This site also contains affiliate links. If you click on one of these links, such as for Amazon.com or Magazine-Agent, we will receive a referral fee or commission if you make a purchase from any of our commerce partners. However, we will never know who you are, or what, if anything, you individually purchased. Please be aware that if you do make a purchase with one of our affiliate partners, or from anyone we link to, you will be providing personal information to the seller, but not to us. Any such disclosures will be governed by the privacy policy of the external website.
Large Print Reviews does not actively collect personal information about our users. We currently do not have a newsletter or mailing list, and we do not use cookies. The only way that we can obtain personal information about you is if you contact us by email or some other means. If you choose to contact us, any information we collect about you will be used for internal purposes only, or to reply to your inquiry. We will never give or share your information with a third party.
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing or modifying
information previously provided.
Simply send an email to webmaster [at] largeprintreviews [dot] com with your request.Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,
you can contact
webmaster
Large Print Reviews
webmaster [at] largeprintreviews [dot] com
About LPR | Affiliate Disclosure | Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions | Site Map
Questions or Comments? Send an email to:
info [at] largeprintreviews [dot] com
